<Sentences><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_0" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>India invaded Pakistan.</Text><Parse>(S (NP (NNP India)) (VP (VBD invaded) (NP (NNP Pakistan))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_1" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>The United States bombed Hiroshima.</Text><Parse>(S (NP (DT The) (NNP United) (NNPS States)) (VP (VBD bombed) (NP (NNP Hiroshima))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_2" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>Iran held elections.</Text><Parse>(S (NP (NNP Iran)) (VP (VBD held) (NP (NNS elections))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_3" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>The World Bank gave African countries aid.</Text><Parse>(S (NP (DT The) (NNP World) (NNP Bank)) (VP (VBD gave) (NP (JJ African) (NNS countries)) (NP (NN aid))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_4" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>Russia has announced that it intends to honor a 2010 agreement with Iran to sell advanced missile systems.</Text><Parse>(S (NP (NNP Russia)) (VP (VBZ has) (VP (VBN announced) (SBAR (IN that) (S (NP (PRP it)) (VP (VBZ intends) (S (VP (TO to) (VP (VB honor) (NP (NP (DT a) (CD 2010) (NN agreement)) (PP (IN with) (NP (NNP Iran)))) (S (VP (TO to) (VP (VB sell) (NP (JJ advanced) (NN missile) (NNS systems))))))))))))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_5" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>President Barack Obama and President Raul Castro met in Panama.</Text><Parse>(S (NP (NP (NNP President) (NNP Barack) (NNP Obama)) (CC and) (NP (NNP President) (NNP Raul) (NNP Castro))) (VP (VBD met) (PP (IN in) (NP (NNP Panama)))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_6" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>The US leader prepares to attend the Beijing Olympics, an event which will test his vow to keep politics out of the Games. </Text><Parse>(S (NP (DT The) (NNP US) (NN leader)) (VP (VBZ prepares) (S (VP (TO to) (VP (VB attend) (NP (NP (DT the) (NNP Beijing) (NNPS Olympics)) (, ,) (NP (NP (DT an) (NN event)) (SBAR (WHNP (WDT which)) (S (VP (MD will) (VP (VB test) (NP (PRP$ his) (NN vow) (S (VP (TO to) (VP (VB keep) (NP (NNS politics)) (ADVP (IN out) (PP (IN of) (NP (DT the) (NNPS Games)))))))))))))))))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_7" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>A powerful earthquake devastates Nepal.</Text><Parse>(S (NP (DT A) (JJ powerful) (NN earthquake)) (VP (VBZ devastates) (NP (NNP Nepal))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_8" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>A court in Guyana has issued arrest warrants to two Brazilian men sought in the brutal slaying of two American missionaries in southern Guyana three years ago, a senior Guyanese police officer said Wednesday. </Text><Parse>(S (S (NP (NP (DT A) (NN court)) (PP (IN in) (NP (NNP Guyana)))) (VP (VBZ has) (VP (VBN issued) (NP (NN arrest) (NNS warrants)) (PP (TO to) (NP (NP (CD two) (JJ Brazilian) (NNS men)) (VP (VBN sought) (PP (IN in) (NP (NP (DT the) (JJ brutal) (NN slaying)) (PP (IN of) (NP (NP (CD two) (JJ American) (NNS missionaries)) (PP (IN in) (NP (JJ southern) (NNP Guyana))) (ADVP (NP (CD three) (NNS years)) (RB ago)))))))))))) (, ,) (NP (DT a) (JJ senior) (JJ Guyanese) (NN police) (NN officer)) (VP (VBD said) (NP-TMP (NNP Wednesday))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_9" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>China remains mum on the Islamic republic and Russia's UN ambassador said he was unaware of such agreement. </Text><Parse>(S (S (NP (NNP China)) (VP (VBZ remains) (ADJP (JJ mum) (PP (IN on) (NP (DT the) (JJ Islamic) (NN republic)))))) (CC and) (S (NP (NP (NNP Russia) (POS 's)) (NNP UN) (NN ambassador)) (VP (VBD said) (SBAR (S (NP (PRP he)) (VP (VBD was) (ADJP (JJ unaware) (PP (IN of) (NP (JJ such) (NN agreement))))))))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_10" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>The statement by the French presidency comes a day before Sarkozy heads to Beijing for the Friday opening of the Olympic Games, seeking to mend ties with China frayed by an initial threat to boycott the ceremony. </Text><Parse>(S (NP (NP (DT The) (NN statement)) (PP (IN by) (NP (DT the) (JJ French) (NN presidency)))) (VP (VBZ comes) (NP (DT a) (NN day)) (PP (IN before) (NP (NNP Sarkozy) (NNS heads))) (PP (TO to) (NP (NP (NNP Beijing)) (PP (IN for) (NP (NP (DT the) (NNP Friday) (NN opening)) (PP (IN of) (NP (DT the) (NNP Olympic) (NNPS Games))))))) (, ,) (S (VP (VBG seeking) (S (VP (TO to) (VP (VB mend) (NP (NNS ties)) (PP (IN with) (NP (NP (NNP China)) (VP (VBN frayed) (PP (IN by) (NP (DT an) (JJ initial) (NN threat))) (PP (TO to) (NP (NP (NN boycott)) (NP (DT the) (NN ceremony))))))))))))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_11" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>A Tunisian court has jailed a man for two years for helping young militants join an armed Islamic group in Lebanon, his lawyer said Wednesday. </Text><Parse>(S (S (NP (DT A) (JJ Tunisian) (NN court)) (VP (VBZ has) (VP (VBN jailed) (NP (NP (DT a) (NN man)) (PP (IN for) (NP (CD two) (NNS years)))) (PP (IN for) (S (VP (VBG helping) (SBAR (S (NP (JJ young) (NNS militants)) (VP (VBP join) (NP (NP (DT an) (JJ armed) (JJ Islamic) (NN group)) (PP (IN in) (NP (NNP Lebanon))))))))))))) (, ,) (NP (PRP$ his) (NN lawyer)) (VP (VBD said) (NP-TMP (NNP Wednesday))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_12" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>France on Wednesday condemned unacceptable allegations by Rwanda that it had played an active role in the 1994 genocide, as Kigali said it hoped French officials would be indicted for war crimes. </Text><Parse>(S (NP (NP (NNP France)) (PP (IN on) (NP (NNP Wednesday)))) (VP (VBD condemned) (NP (ADJP (JJ unacceptable)) (NNS allegations)) (PP (IN by) (NP (NNP Rwanda))) (SBAR (IN that) (S (NP (PRP it)) (VP (VBD had) (VP (VBN played) (NP (NP (DT an) (JJ active) (NN role)) (PP (IN in) (NP (DT the) (CD 1994) (NN genocide)))) (, ,) (SBAR (IN as) (S (NP (NNP Kigali)) (VP (VBD said) (SBAR (S (NP (PRP it)) (VP (VBD hoped) (SBAR (S (NP (JJ French) (NNS officials)) (VP (MD would) (VP (VB be) (VP (VBN indicted) (PP (IN for) (NP (NN war) (NNS crimes))))))))))))))))))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_13" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>A 500-page report released Tuesday in the Rwandan capital alleged that France was aware of preparations for the genocide, and that the French military in Rwanda helped to plan and carry out killings.</Text><Parse>(S (NP (NP (DT A) (JJ 500-page) (NN report)) (VP (VBN released) (NP-TMP (NNP Tuesday)) (PP (IN in) (NP (DT the) (JJ Rwandan) (NN capital))))) (VP (VBD alleged) (SBAR (SBAR (IN that) (S (NP (NNP France)) (VP (VBD was) (ADJP (JJ aware) (PP (IN of) (NP (NP (NNS preparations)) (PP (IN for) (NP (DT the) (NN genocide))))))))) (, ,) (CC and) (SBAR (IN that) (S (NP (NP (DT the) (JJ French) (NN military)) (PP (IN in) (NP (NNP Rwanda)))) (VP (VBD helped) (S (VP (TO to) (VP (VP (VB plan)) (CC and) (VP (VB carry) (PRT (RP out)) (NP (NNS killings))))))))))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_14" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>Israel on Wednesday released the mayor of the northern West Bank city of Nablus, a member of the Islamist Hamas movement jailed over a year ago, Palestinian security officials said. </Text><Parse>(S (S (NP (NP (NNP Israel)) (PP (IN on) (NP (NNP Wednesday)))) (VP (VBD released) (NP (NP (DT the) (NN mayor)) (PP (IN of) (NP (NP (DT the) (JJ northern) (NNP West) (NNP Bank) (NN city)) (PP (IN of) (NP (NP (NNP Nablus)) (, ,) (NP (NP (DT a) (NN member)) (PP (IN of) (NP (NP (DT the) (JJ Islamist) (NNP Hamas) (NN movement)) (VP (VBN jailed) (PP (IN over) (ADVP (NP (DT a) (NN year)) (RB ago)))))))))))))) (, ,) (NP (JJ Palestinian) (NN security) (NNS officials)) (VP (VBD said)) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_15" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>The release of Adli Yaish, who had been arrested 15 months ago, came as Israel announced it would free over 150 Palestinian prisoners by the end of August as a goodwill gesture to Palestinian president Mahmud Abbas. </Text><Parse>(S (NP (NP (DT The) (NN release)) (PP (IN of) (NP (NNP Adli) (NNP Yaish))) (, ,) (SBAR (WHNP (WP who)) (S (VP (VBD had) (VP (VBN been) (VP (VBN arrested) (ADVP (NP (CD 15) (NNS months)) (RB ago))))))) (, ,)) (VP (VBD came) (SBAR (IN as) (S (NP (NNP Israel)) (VP (VBD announced) (SBAR (S (NP (PRP it)) (VP (MD would) (VP (VB free) (NP (QP (IN over) (CD 150)) (JJ Palestinian) (NNS prisoners)) (PP (IN by) (NP (NP (DT the) (NN end)) (PP (IN of) (NP (NNP August))))) (PP (IN as) (NP (NP (DT a) (NN goodwill) (NN gesture)) (PP (TO to) (NP (JJ Palestinian) (NN president) (NNP Mahmud) (NNP Abbas))))))))))))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_16" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>General David Petraeus held talks with President Michel Sleiman during a surprise visit to Beirut on Wednesday, offering further military support to Lebanon. </Text><Parse>(S (NP (NNP General) (NNP David) (NNP Petraeus)) (VP (VBD held) (NP (NNS talks)) (PP (IN with) (NP (NP (NNP President) (NNP Michel) (NNP Sleiman)) (PP (IN during) (NP (DT a) (NN surprise) (NN visit))))) (PP (TO to) (NP (NP (NNP Beirut)) (PP (IN on) (NP (NNP Wednesday))))) (, ,) (S (VP (VBG offering) (NP (JJ further) (JJ military) (NN support)) (PP (TO to) (NP (NNP Lebanon)))))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_17" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>US and British activists staged a dramatic protest in Beijing on Wednesday, scaling a pole and unfurling giant ''Free Tibet'' banners close to the stadium where the Olympics will open in two days. </Text><Parse>(S (NP (NP (NNP US) (CC and) (NNP British)) (NNS activists)) (VP (VBD staged) (NP (DT a) (JJ dramatic) (NN protest)) (PP (IN in) (NP (NNP Beijing))) (PP (IN on) (NP (NNP Wednesday))) (, ,) (VP (VP (VBG scaling) (NP (DT a) (NN pole))) (CC and) (VP (VBG unfurling) (NP (JJ giant)) ('' '')) (NP (NP (NNP Free) (NNP Tibet)) ('' '') (PP (ADVP (NP (NNS banners)) (RB close)) (TO to) (NP (NP (DT the) (NN stadium)) (SBAR (WHADVP (WRB where)) (S (NP (DT the) (NNPS Olympics)) (VP (MD will) (VP (VB open) (PP (IN in) (NP (CD two) (NNS days)))))))))))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_18" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>Rwanda's information minister said Wednesday she hoped a raft of French political and military officials accused of playing a role in the country's 1994 genocide would soon be indicted for war crimes. </Text><Parse>(S (NP (NP (NNP Rwanda) (POS 's)) (NN information) (NN minister)) (VP (VBD said) (NP-TMP (NNP Wednesday)) (SBAR (S (NP (PRP she)) (VP (VBD hoped) (SBAR (S (NP (NP (DT a) (NN raft)) (PP (IN of) (NP (ADJP (JJ French) (JJ political)) (CC and) (NP (JJ military) (NNS officials))))) (VP (VBD accused) (PP (IN of) (S (VP (VBG playing) (SBAR (S (NP (NP (DT a) (NN role)) (PP (IN in) (NP (NP (DT the) (NN country) (POS 's)) (CD 1994) (NN genocide)))) (VP (MD would) (ADVP (RB soon)) (VP (VB be) (VP (VBN indicted) (PP (IN for) (NP (NN war) (NNS crimes)))))))))))))))))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_19" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>France on Wednesday accused Rwanda of making unacceptable accusations by alleging Paris played an active role in the 1994 genocide, but said it was still determined to mend damaged ties with Kigali. </Text><Parse>(S (NP (NP (NNP France)) (PP (IN on) (NP (NNP Wednesday)))) (VP (VBD accused) (NP (NP (NNP Rwanda)) (PP (IN of) (S (VP (VBG making) (NP (ADJP (JJ unacceptable)) (NNS accusations)) (PP (IN by) (S (VP (VBG alleging) (SBAR (S (NP (NNP Paris)) (VP (VP (VBD played) (NP (DT an) (JJ active) (NN role)) (PP (IN in) (NP (DT the) (CD 1994) (NN genocide)))) (, ,) (CC but) (VP (VBD said) (SBAR (S (NP (PRP it)) (VP (VBD was) (ADVP (RB still)) (VP (VBN determined) (S (VP (TO to) (VP (VB mend) (NP (JJ damaged) (NNS ties)) (PP (IN with) (NP (NNP Kigali)))))))))))))))))))))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_20" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>Gunmen opens fire on Mexico army chopper as violence roils major state.</Text><Parse>(S (NP (NNS Gunmen)) (VP (VBZ opens) (NP (NN fire)) (PP (IN on) (NP (NNP Mexico) (NN army) (NN chopper))) (SBAR (IN as) (S (NP (NN violence)) (VP (VBZ roils) (NP (JJ major) (NN state)))))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_21" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>Before leaving for Beijing on Thursday, Bush was scheduled to give a speech here on US relations with Asia and meet with exiled dissidents from military-ruled Myanmar. </Text><Parse>(S (PP (IN Before) (S (VP (VBG leaving) (PP (IN for) (NP (NNP Beijing))) (PP (IN on) (NP (NNP Thursday)))))) (, ,) (NP (NNP Bush)) (VP (VBD was) (VP (VBN scheduled) (S (VP (TO to) (VP (VP (VB give) (NP (DT a) (NN speech)) (ADVP (RB here)) (PP (IN on) (NP (NNP US) (NNS relations))) (PP (IN with) (NP (NNP Asia)))) (CC and) (VP (VB meet) (PP (IN with) (NP (NP (VBN exiled) (NNS dissidents)) (PP (IN from) (NP (JJ military-ruled) (NNP Myanmar))))))))))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_22" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>North Korean diplomats disrupt human rights panel.</Text><Parse>(S (NP (ADJP (JJ North) (JJ Korean)) (NNS diplomats)) (VP (VBP disrupt) (NP (JJ human) (NNS rights) (NN panel))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_23" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>Armed groups dominate Congolese illicit Golad trade.</Text><Parse>(S (NP (VBN Armed) (NNS groups)) (VP (VBP dominate) (NP (JJ Congolese) (JJ illicit) (NP (NNP Golad)) (NN trade))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_24" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>Venezuela raises minimum wage 30 pct amid raging inflation.</Text><Parse>(S (NP (NNP Venezuela)) (VP (VBZ raises) (NP (JJ minimum) (NN wage) (NP (CD 30) (NN pct))) (PP (IN amid) (S (VP (VBG raging) (NP (NN inflation)))))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_25" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>China passes Mexico as the top source of new U.S. immigrants.</Text><Parse>(S (NP (NNP China)) (VP (VBZ passes) (NP (NP (NNP Mexico)) (PP (IN as) (NP (NP (DT the) (JJ top) (NN source)) (PP (IN of) (NP (JJ new) (NNP U.S.) (NNS immigrants))))))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_26" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>Navy starts to accompany U.S. ships in strait of Hormuz.</Text><Parse>(S (NP (NNP Navy)) (VP (VBZ starts) (S (VP (TO to) (VP (VB accompany) (NP (NNP U.S.) (NNS ships)) (PP (IN in) (NP (NP (NN strait)) (PP (IN of) (NP (NNP Hormuz))))))))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_27" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>Bird flu outbreak prompts state of emergency in Iowa.</Text><Parse>(S (NP (NN Bird) (NN flu) (NN outbreak)) (VP (VBZ prompts) (NP (NP (NN state)) (PP (IN of) (NP (NP (NN emergency)) (PP (IN in) (NP (NNP Iowa))))))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_28" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>Supreme Court upholds fundraising restriction on judicial elections.</Text><Parse>(S (NP (NNP Supreme) (NNP Court)) (VP (VBZ upholds) (S (VP (VBG fundraising) (NP (NN restriction)) (PP (IN on) (NP (JJ judicial) (NNS elections)))))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_29" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>White House says the FBI's help on ransom is not a policy violation.</Text><Parse>(S (NP (NNP White) (NNP House)) (VP (VBZ says) (SBAR (S (NP (NP (NP (DT the) (NNP FBI) (POS 's)) (NN help)) (PP (IN on) (NP (NN ransom)))) (VP (VBZ is) (RB not) (NP (DT a) (NN policy) (NN violation)))))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_30" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>Mary Lyon saw you coming.</Text><Parse>(S (NP (NNP Mary) (NNP Lyon)) (VP (VBD saw) (S (NP (PRP you)) (VP (VBG coming)))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_31" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>I survived the housing lottery.</Text><Parse>(S (NP (PRP I)) (VP (VBD survived) (NP (DT the) (NN housing) (NN lottery))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_32" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>Autocorrect corrects Moodle to Noodle.</Text><Parse>(S (NP (NN Autocorrect)) (VP (VBZ corrects) (NP (NP (NNP Moodle)) (PP (TO to) (NP (NNP Noodle))))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_33" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>Just when the toilet paper here couldn't get any thinner, it did.</Text><Parse>(S (SBAR (RB Just) (WHADVP (WRB when)) (S (NP (DT the) (NN toilet) (NN paper)) (ADVP (RB here)) (VP (MD could) (RB n't) (VP (VB get) (NP (DT any) (JJR thinner)))))) (, ,) (NP (PRP it)) (VP (VBD did)) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_34" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>Officially done with college!</Text><Parse>(S (VP (ADVP (RB Officially)) (VBN done) (PP (IN with) (NP (NN college)))) (. !))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_35" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>Just want my professor to grade this exam, have an Oprah moment and say, 'You get an A, and you get an A, everybody gets an A!'</Text><Parse>(S (S (VP (VP (ADVP (RB Just)) (VB want) (NP (PRP$ my) (NN professor)) (PP (TO to) (NP (NN grade))) (SBAR (S (NP (DT this) (NN exam)) (, ,) (VP (VBP have) (NP (DT an) (NNP Oprah) (NN moment)))))) (CC and) (VP (VB say) (, ,) (`` `) (S (S (NP (PRP You)) (VP (VBP get) (NP (DT an) (NN A)))) (, ,) (CC and) (S (NP (PRP you)) (VP (VBP get) (NP (DT an) (NN A)))))))) (, ,) (NP (NN everybody)) (VP (VBZ gets) (NP (DT an) (NN A))) (. !) ('' '))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_36" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>My concentration level is almost as bad as my need for summer.</Text><Parse>(S (NP (PRP$ My) (NN concentration) (NN level)) (VP (VBZ is) (ADJP (ADJP (RB almost) (RB as) (JJ bad)) (PP (IN as) (NP (NP (PRP$ my) (NN need)) (PP (IN for) (NP (NN summer))))))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_37" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>I wish there were designated nap areas around campus.</Text><Parse>(S (NP (PRP I)) (VP (VBP wish) (SBAR (S (NP (EX there)) (VP (VBD were) (VP (VBN designated) (NP (NN nap) (NNS areas)) (PP (IN around) (NP (NN campus)))))))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_38" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>I will pay for your Chipotle order!</Text><Parse>(S (NP (PRP I)) (VP (MD will) (VP (VB pay) (PP (IN for) (NP (PRP$ your) (NNP Chipotle) (NN order))))) (. !))</Parse></Sentence><Sentence date="20150422" id="CMAK_39" sentence="True" source="CMAK"><Text>Failing your classes doesn't mean you're a loser.</Text><Parse>(S (S (VP (VBG Failing) (NP (PRP$ your) (NNS classes)))) (VP (VBZ does) (RB n't) (VP (VB mean) (SBAR (S (NP (PRP you)) (VP (VBP 're) (NP (DT a) (NN loser))))))) (. .))</Parse></Sentence></Sentences>